social-bookmarking.net 2011-09-26

# Privacy Policy | Social Bookmarking .Net

## Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?  

We collect information from you when you register on our site.   

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..  

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.   

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 15.03.2010  

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

Martin Junker  
Hermann-Kauffmann-Str. 8b  
D-22307 Hamburg  
Germany  
+49 160 / 927 08 611

Privacy Policy Created by [Free Privacy Policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/)
